Dr Rustom: Atah ṣaḍaṅganyāsa.
Dr Rustom: Atah ṣaḍaṅganyāsa.
Now we purify the six parts of the body.
Teraz oczyszczamy sześć części ciała.
Shri Mataji: Yes, we have to clear the six parts of our body.
Shri Mataji: Tak, musimy oczyścić sześć części naszego ciała.
Dr Rustom: First, the heart.
Dr Rustom: Najpierw serce.
Shri Mataji: To the heart.
Shri Mataji: Do serca.
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha hitayaya namah
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha hitayaya namah
Dr Rustom: Next the top of the head.
Dr Rustom: Następnie czubek głowy.
Shri Mataji: That is, we bow to our heart.
Shri Mataji: To znaczy, kłaniamy się naszemu sercu.
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha shirse swaha
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha shirse swaha
Shri Mataji: Sahasrara.
Shri Mataji: Sahasrara.
Dr Rustom: Then the Back Agnya.
Dr Rustom: Następnie Tylna Agnya.
OM bhur bhuva swaha shikayaya vashat
OM bhur bhuva swaha shikayaya vashat
Shri Mataji: ‘Vashat’ is like this. [Shri Mataji claps her hands]
Shri Mataji: „Vashat” jest tak. [Shri Mataji klaszcze w dłonie]
That means you bring two fingers, bring it round and hit it hard,
To znaczy, że bierzesz dwa palce, obracasz i uderzasz mocno,
on the Sahasrara [on the palm of the hand].
w Sahasrarę [w dłoń].
That is taking out the baddha, you see.
To wyciąga baddha.
From here, take it out and put it on the Sahasrara, hit it hard.
Stąd to wyciągasz i kładziesz na Sahasrarze, uderzasz mocno.
And this is the ‘Samhara Shakti’ of Shri Krishna [destructive power].
I to jest „Samhara Shakti” Shri Krishny [niszczycielska moc].
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha kavacha aham
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha kavacha aham
Shri Mataji: Kavach. Kavach is bandhan.
Shri Mataji: Kavach. Kavach to bandhan.
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha netrayaa vashat
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha netrayaa vashat
Shri Mataji: You see, eyes are cleansed; must have clean eyes.
Shri Mataji: Widzisz, oczy są oczyszczone; trzeba mieć czyste oczy.
Again, with the clean eyes you again go back at the Agnya, at the Back and take it down.
Znowu, z czystymi oczami wracasz do Agnyi, z Tyłu i ściągasz to w dół.
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha astra vaphat.
Dr Rustom: OM bhur bhuva swaha astra vaphat.
Shri Mataji: Astra. Astra are the weapons that you have got. Astra vaphat!
Shri Mataji: Astra to broń, którą posiadacie. Astra vaphat!
[Shri Mataji claps]. Means all the baddhas should run away.
[Shri Mataji klaszcze]. Co oznacza, że wszystkie baddha powinny uciec.
Dr Rustom: Now the bandhan: ‘Iti dig bandhan’.
Dr Rustom: Teraz bandhan: „Iti dig bandhan”.
[Shri Mataji speaks in Hindi]
[Shri Mataji mówi w hindi]
Shri Mataji: Kavach – Kavach is the cover, Kavach is the cover.
Shri Mataji: Kavach – Kavach to osłona, Kavach to osłona.
Dr Rustom: Shield like.
Dr Rustom: Jak tarcza.
Shri Mataji: Shield, shield, shield, Kavach. Kavach is shield, sorry. Kavach is shield!
Shri Mataji: Tarcza, tarcza, tarcza, Kavach. Kavach to tarcza, przepraszam. Kavach to tarcza!
[Hindi] And this is bandhan, sorry.
[Hindi] A to jest bandhan, przepraszam.
Dr Rustom: Rigvedah, yejurvedah, sam-vedah yatharvana
Dr Rustom: Rigvedah, yejurvedah, sam-vedah yatharvana
angeshcha sahitah sarve kalasham tu samashritah
angeshcha sahitah sarve kalasham tu samashritah
Atra gayatri savitri shanti pushti kare tatha ayantu deva pujarthan durita kshayakarakaha.
Atra gayatri savitri shanti pushti kare tatha ayantu deva pujarthan durita kshayakarakaha.